<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<document xmlns="http://di.tamu.edu/DRI/1.0/" xmlns:i18n="http://apache.org/cocoon/i18n/2.1" version="1.1">
    <body>
        <div id="file.news.div.news" n="news" rend="primary news-div">
            <head>REF Compliance Checker Demonstrator</head>
            <div id="file.news.div.news1" n="news1" rend="news-div">
                <p>Welcome to the REF Compliance Checker Demonstrator repository. In this repository you can test tools created
                    to assist institutions to comply with the
                    <xref target="http://www.hefce.ac.uk/pubs/year/2014/201407/">
                        audit requirements for Open access in the post-2014 Research Excellence Framework (REF)
                    </xref>.
                </p>
                <p>This installation of DSpace 5.6 has been enhanced with the <xref target="https://github.com/atmire/RIOXX/">Atmire RIOXX patch</xref> and a number of new developments including:</p>
                <list>
                    <item>REF specific metadata: Date of First Compliant Deposit (FCD), Version of FCD, Date of First compliant Open Access (FOA) and REF target panel.</item>
                    <item>REF accepted exceptions, including technical exceptions, access exceptions, deposit exceptions and other exceptions.</item>
                    <item>REF Compliance checks for Conference Papers/Proceeding/Abstract and Journal Article/Review
                        <list>
                            <item>During submission</item>
                            <item>In workflow review</item>
                            <item>On archived items</item>
                        </list>
                    </item>
                    <item>RIOXX Compliance checks
                        <list>
                            <item>During submission</item>
                            <item>In workflow review</item>
                            <item>On archived items</item>
                        </list>
                    </item>
                </list>
            </div>
            <div id="file.news.div.news2" n="news2" rend="news-div">
                <head>Current development phase: REF Compliance Checker v1 Released</head>
                <p>Following credentials can be used to log in and test the functionality:</p>
                <p>
                    <table n="table1" id="credentials-table" rows="2" cols="2">
                        <row>
                            <cell><hi rend="bold">Submitting new items</hi></cell>
                            <cell><xref target="mailto:ref-submitter@example.com">ref-submitter@example.com</xref></cell>
                        </row>
                        <row>
                            <cell><hi rend="bold">Reviewing items in workflow</hi></cell>
                            <cell><xref target="mailto:ref-reviewer@example.com">ref-reviewer@example.com</xref></cell>
                        </row>
                    </table>
                </p>
                <p>Password: The password for both of these accounts is the abbreviation of &quot;Higher Education Funding Council for England&quot;, in lowercase.</p>
                <p>You can report your questions, comments and other feedback on the Github Issues page:</p>
                <p><xref target="https://github.com/atmire/REF/issues">https://github.com/atmire/REF/issues</xref></p>
                <p>The community feedback phase was extended to <hi rend="bold">August 31st</hi>. After this feedback phase, Atmire resolved the final issues and made the source code available for DSpace 4 &amp; 5.</p>
            </div>
            <div id="file.news.div.news3" n="news3" rend="news-div">
                <head>When can I install this functionality in my DSpace?</head>
                <p>The code for these features and deployment instructions are available on Github: <xref target="https://github.com/atmire/REF">https://github.com/atmire/REF</xref></p>
                <p>Detailed installation instructions and additional documentation can be found in the <xref target="https://github.com/atmire/REF/blob/master/README.md">README.md</xref> file.</p>
            </div>
            <div id="file.news.div.news4" n="news4" rend="news-div">
                <head>Email disabled</head>
                <p>Outgoing email has been disabled on this demonstrator.</p>
            </div>
            <div id="file.news.div.news5" n="news5" rend="news-div">
                <head>More information</head>
                <p>Any question or comment about this demonstrator can be sent to info at atmire.com</p>
            </div>
        </div>
    </body>
    <options/>
    <meta>
        <userMeta/>
        <pageMeta/>
        <repositoryMeta/>
    </meta>
</document>
